Testosterone
Also known
as the male hormone
Men who've hit puberty
pump it out almost
their whole lives
Our bodies release
a by-product of
this hormone
through sweat glands
It causes a sour
unpleasant odor
[Male Hormone Heaven
Daemun High]
Last summer
was hell to endure
Hey, Il-tak
You smell really good
What?
- Hey!
- S***
- Stay still, okay?
- Let go!
I'm going to beat you up
if you don't
Just let me
smell you a little
After that, this jerk
spent the entire day
smelling me
F***
Should I get
a stinky perfume?
That's it!
I'm sorry
I got soaked
while washing my face
Could I borrow
your hoodie?
Is this the scent
of an apex predator?
It might not be so bad
after all…